Atobajaye Oluwatobiloba

Ondo, Nigeria



atobajayetobiloba@gmail.com



09091605273



linkedin.com/in/atobajayeoluwatobiloba-930a8b190

Summary

Experienced Senior Creative Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the Digital industry. I am a UI/ UX designer with experience in brand identification, communication tools, and WordPress Website development. Projects requiring a high level of vision, problem-solving, and aesthetic polish are generally what I gravitate towards. In my experience, the finest products are produced when partners and stakeholders are closely involved throughout the design process. I am very good at designing solutions to problems, especially for digital (Web and App) platforms. I am also skilled in Graphic Design, Brand Design, Teamwork, and Microsoft Excel.

Experience



Brand Designer

TMA clothings

Feb 2022 - Present (6 months +)

- Identify the brand message then work on various marketing tools, such as logos, that convey the intended message.
- Creating identities for the business and its products.

Senior Product Designer

TMA clothings

Feb 2022 - Present (6 months +)

I oversee the design process of their product(T-shirts, caps, sweaters, hoodies etc.) from start to finish.

Graphic Designer

Freelance

Jul 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

- Strong understanding of visual design, branding, user experience design, and user interface.
- Communicate with customers to develop designs that portray an intended message.
- · Advise clients on strategies to engage target audiences
- Identify the best ways to illustrate and communicate clients' vision while complying with design best practices



Senior Creative Designer

Zowe graphics

May 2018 - Present (4 years 3 months +)

- Design logos and other graphics as well as in-store brandings such as merchandise displays and packaging.
- · Create visual concepts
- Communicate ideas that inspire, inform, and captivate consumers.

Wordpress Developer

aromaofbowie

Jun 2022 - Jul 2022 (2 months)

I designed their restaurant website of 6pages with order and reservation services on WordPress. I worked with their specifications to ensure I meet the objectives they created for their restaurant. I also added a preloader and a popup to make the website more converting.

Wordpress Developer

Abundant Grace Chapel International

May 2022 - May 2022 (1 month)

I designed a church website of 8pages which included the Home page, About us page, Our Mission, Past sermons, Live sermons, Donation Pages, Ministry Page and Get Involved page. I included a live chat on the website, Integrated it with a payment option. I made the site responsive to all devices, I also made it speed optimized. the website also contains images of events in the church.

Brand Designer

Debbie Fashion House

Feb 2021 - Feb 2022 (1 year 1 month)

- In charge of putting together fashion labels' products, brand messaging and the lifestyle they're trying to sell to form a distinct brand identity.
- Creating marketing materials like posters, social media posts and lookbooks.

Education



Federal University of Technology Akure

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, building technology 2016 - 2021

Skills

Branding • Adobe Photoshop • Visual Design • Web Development • WordPress • Web Design • Teamwork • Graphic Design • Brand Design • Crafts